The Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection 1903-2012 (Bulk 1970-2000) MSS 040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2003 - Series VI: Major Projects
  - Subseries A: "The Art and Flair of Mary Blair"
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Smith, Lella, undated (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Thomas, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Tieman, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS World's Fair: It's a Small World, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Subseries B: Vladimir (William) Tytla, "Animation's Michelangelo"
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1975-1988 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, undated (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Various, undated (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Disney Giant (biography of Tytla), undated (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Interview (cassette tape), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Photos, undated (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Tytla, Peter, undated (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Tytla, Peter: Animation Journal, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Animation's Michelangelo, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Biographical information, untited (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Cinefastique (v.5 no.3), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Art Babbitt, 1933-1965 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: John Cannemaker, 1975-1995 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Walt Disney, 1994-1956 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Family, 1929-1939 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Various, 1929-1968 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Diseny production documents, undated (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Interviews, undated (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: News articles, 1940-1995 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Promotional Folder: Katonah Museum of Art, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Research notes (Canemaker), undated (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Subseries C: "Walt Disney's Nine Old Men and the Art of Animation"
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to book, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to book, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Canemaker, John: Research materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Clark, Les, undated (Box 6, Folder 242-244)
    - Davis, Marc, undated (Box 6, Folder 245-248)
    - FRANK AND OLLIE, undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Johnston, Ollie, undated (Box 6, Folder 250-252)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated (Box 6, Folder 253-254)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated (Box 7, Folder 255-257)
    - Kimball, Ward, undated (Box 7, Folder 258-260)
    - Larson, Eric, undated (Box 7, Folder 261-263)
    - Lounsbery, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Reigherman, Wolfgang, undated (Box 7, Folder 265-266)
    - Thomas, Frank, undated (Box 7, Folder 267-272)
- Accretions 2003 - Oversize - Series II: Graphic Material
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork
    - Babbitt, Art, undated (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Blair, Mary: "Art and Flair of Mary Blair" (galley proofs), undated (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Blair, Mary: Assorted, undated (Box 8, Folder 96-97)
    - Blair, Mary: Christmas card designs, undated (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Blair, Mary: Commercial art, undated (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Blair, Mary: It's a Small World, undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Clark, Les, undated (Box 8, Folder 109-110)
    - Davis, Marc, undated (Box 8, Folder 111-112)
    - Ferguson, Norman, undated (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Iwerks, Ub, undated (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Johnston, Ollie, undated (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated (Box 9, Folder 120-122)
    - Kimball, Ward, undated (Box 10, Folder 125-126)
    - Larson, Eric, undated (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Lounsbery, John, undated (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Luske, Ham, undated (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Moore, Fred, undated (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Reitherman, Wolfgang, undated (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Thomas, Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Tytla, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Tytla, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Williams, Richard, undated (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Williams, Richard, undated (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Unknown artist, undated (Box 11, Folder 164)
- Accretions 2008 - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - Animation Articles, 1981 - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Awards: 33rd Annie Awards (LA), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Exhibitions: Animated Art from Walt Disney Studios: The Lucius T. and Jane Scott B. Chapin Collection (Marsh Art Gallery, VA), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Exhibitions: The Art of Fantasia (Cartoon Art Museum, CA), 1990 - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitions: Independent Voices: The Art of Animation (Grand Valley State University, MI), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions: Oscar Howe: A Retrospective Exhibition (Thomas Gilcrease Museum Association, OK), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Exhibitions: Peanuts (Cartoon Research Library, OH), 2000 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Exhibitions: Pixar: 20 Years of Animation (Museum of Modern Art, NY), 2005 - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Exhibitions: Polish Animated Film (Museum of Modern Art, NY), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Exhibitions: Tanja Softic': Recent Works on Paper (Marsh Art Gallery, VA), 1981 - 2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Exhibitions: Vilallonga: Poetic Symbolism from Barcelona (City of Thousand Oaks, CA), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Anima Mundi (Brazil) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Animadrid (Spain), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Animadrid (Spain), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Annecy (France), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Festivals & Screenings: The Cartoon Medicine Show: Animated Cartoons from the Collection of the National Library of Medicine (National Library of Medicine, DC), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 41st Chicago International Film Festival (IL), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Fantoche (Switzerland), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Festival du Court Metrage de Clermont-Ferrand (France), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Festivals & Screenings: I Castelli Animati (Italy) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 21st International Short Film Festival Berlin (Germany), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Festivals & Screenings: JazzToons with John Canemaker (Jacob Burns Film Center, NY), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Les Sommets du Cinema D'Animation (Canada), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Margaret Mead Film & Video Festival (NY), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Ottawa Student Animation Festival (Canada), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Ottawa International Animation Festival (Canada), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 13th Stuttgart International Festival of Animated Film (Germany), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 32nd Telluride Film Festival (CO) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 33rd Telluride Film Festival (CO) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Festivals & Screenings: VisionFest (Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis, IN), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 17th World Festival of Animated Film (Croatia), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - "Avoid Eye Contact" NYC Independent Animation Panel, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Associazione Fabrizio Bellocchio Onlus, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Cartoon Research Library, Ohio State University, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: 1998 Fall & Holiday Preview (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: Summer Preview 2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: 2005 Preview (Electronic press kit) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: ANTZ, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: CHICKEN RUN, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: MADAGASCAR (Electronic press kit), 2005 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: OVER THE HEDGE (Electronic press kit), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: PRINCE OF EGYPT, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: THE ROAD TO EL DORADO, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SHARK TALE (Electronic press kit), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SHREK, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SINBAD: LEGEND OF THE SEVEN SEAS, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SPIRIT: STALLION OF THE CIMARRON, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Go Fish Pictures: GHOST IN THE SHELL 2: INNOCENCE, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Go Fish Pictures: MILLENNIUM ACTRESS, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - iotaCenter, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - The OpenEnded Group (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Pacific Film Archive, University of California ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2006
    - Pixar Animation Studios: Exhibition ***see*** Series I-A, Box 1, Folder 8, 2005 - 2006
    - Pixar Animation Studios: CARS (Electronic press kit), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: FINDING NEMO, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: THE INCREDIBLES, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: THE INCREDIBLES (Electronic press kit), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: TOY STORY 2, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Soup2Nuts, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Studio Ghibli: HOWL'S MOVING CASTLE, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Studio Ghibli: MIYAZAKI'S SPIRITED AWAY, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Twentieth Century Fox: ANASTASIA, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Vanguard Animation Studios: VALIANT, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Babbitt, Art, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Bellocchio, Fabrizio ***see*** Series I-A, Box 1, Folder 33, n.d.
    - Canemaker, John: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2002 - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Canemaker, John: Miscellaneous Publicity, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Canemaker, John: Winsor McCay: His Life and Art (Revised & Expanded Edition), 2005 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Chomet, Sylvain: THE TRIPLETS OF BELLEVILLE, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Davis, Marc, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Disney, Walt: Annual Report, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Disney, Walt: Annual Report, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Disney, Walt: Canemaker article on closing of Disney's last hand-drawn animation studio, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Disney, Walt: Inter-office memo written by Walt Disney, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Disney, Walt: ATLANTIS: THE LOST EMPIRE, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Disney, Walt: BROTHER BEAR, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Disney, Walt: CHICKEN LITTLE (Electronic press kit), 2005 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Disney, Walt: THE CHRONICLES OF NARNIA: THE LION, THE WITCH AND THE WARDROBE (Electronic press kit), 2005 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Disney, Walt: THE EMPEROR'S NEW GROOVE, 2000 - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA 2000, 1999 - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Disney, Walt: HERCULES, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Disney, Walt: HOME ON THE RANGE, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Disney, Walt: HOME ON THE RANGE (Electronic press kit), n.d. (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Disney, Walt: THE HUNCHBACK OF NOTRE DAME, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Disney, Walt: LILO & STITCH, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Disney, Walt: MULAN, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Disney, Walt: PIRATES OF THE CARIBBEAN: DEAD MAN'S CHEST (Electronic press kit), 2006 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Disney, Walt: POCAHONTAS, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Disney, Walt: POOH'S HEFFALUMP MOVIE, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Disney, Walt: TARZAN, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Disney, Walt: TEACHER'S PET, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Disney, Walt: TIM BURTON'S THE NIGHTMARE BEFORE CHRISTMAS: Presented for the First Time Ever in Disney Digital 3-D (Electronic press kit), 2006 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Disney, Walt: TREASURE PLANET, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Disney, Walt: THE WILD (Electronic pree kit), 2006 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Disney, Walt: Luca Raffaelli's Le Anime Disegnate: Il pensiero nei cartoon da Disney ai giapponesi e oltre, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Halas, John & Batchelor, Joy, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Hubley, John & Faith: Interview of Faith Hubley, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Hubley, John & Faith: FINIAN'S RAINBOW, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Hurd, Earl, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Hykade, Andreas (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Johnston, Ollie: Correspondence with Canemaker, 1979 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Kley, Heinrich, 1937 - 1939 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Kley, Heinrich, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Majolie, Bianca @ Blanche Hielborn, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Majolie, Bianca @ Blanche Hielborn, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - McCay, Winsor: Canemaker correspondence with Maud H. Brown (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - McCay, Winsor: Canemaker correspondence with Robert W. McCay (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - McCay, Winsor: Canemaker correspondence with Ray Moniz (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - McCay, Winsor: Various correspondences re: McCay (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - McCay, Winsor: Various correspondences re: McCay (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - McCay, Winsor: Interview of William R. Hearst, Jr., 1988 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - McCay, Winsor: Interview of Irving Mendelsohn, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Reiniger, Lotte, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Thomas, Frank: Correspondence with Canemaker ***see*** Johnston, Ollie, 1976 - 2003
    - Zemeckis, Robert: THE POLAR EXPRESS, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Zinnen, Al, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Accretions 2008 - Series II: Graphic Material
  Unless otherwise noted, Series II-A and II-B are in oversize boxes.
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork
    - Canemaker, John: THE FELT FAMILY, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Canemaker, John: Destination Modern Art: An Intergalactic Journey to MoMA and P.S.1, 2005 - 2006 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Various: Presentation slides for "The Moving Image", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Subseries B: Posters
    - Festivals & Screenings, 2005 - 2006 (Box 6, Folder 157)
- Accretions 2008 - Series III: Book Collection
- Accretions 2008 - Series IV: Periodical Collection
  Unless noted below, the periodical collection have been catalogued in Bobcat. A keyword or related name search with the name Canemaker will retrieve the records for the periodicals.
  - Animation P.S.1 (MoMA), 2001 - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - ASIFA, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - ASIFA-EAST, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 156)
- Accretions 2008 - Series V: Audio & Video Tape Collection
  - Subseries B: Original Recordings
    - Recording for FINIAN'S RAINBOW: music & commentary by composer Yip Harburg, Part I, 1954 (Box 7, Media ID: 040.0216)
      Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 90
    - Recording for FINIAN'S RAINBOW: music & commentary by composer Yip Harburg, Part II, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 40.0217)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UDS-II 46
    - Irving Mendelsohn (friend of Winsor McCay) interview by Canemaker; August 1974 | Canemaker at Cinemateque Screening of McCay films: FLYING HOUSE, PET & MOSQUITO PT. 1; August 12, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 40.0218)
      Audiocassette, TDK D*C60
    - Midwest Film Fest, Frank Thomas & Ollie Johnston interview by Canemaker, Part I, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 40.0219)
      Audiocassette, Instant Reply
    - Midwest Film Fest, Frank Thomas & Ollie Johnston interview by Canemaker, Part II, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 40.022)
    - Cannizzaro family watching home movies (later used in Canemaker's THE MOON AND THE SON"); July 3-5, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 40.0221)
      Audiocassette, Supertape Gold 90
    - NPR Interview: Jim D'Anna & John Canemaker; May 7, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 40.0222)
      Audiocassette, Konica ML 90
    - Phone interview with Jean Adams (Daughter of Apthorp Adams, friend of Winsor McCay), recorded by Larry Ruppel and Greg Brown, c. 1986 (Box 7, Folder 40.0223)
      Audiocassette, TDK SA 60
    - Theo Halladay on her mother, Sylvia Maberly-Holland, Los Angeles; December 5, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 40.0224)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UR 90
    - Phone interview with Hal Walker, FELIX THE CAT animator; July 4, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40.0225)
      Audiocassette, Maxell XLII-S 90
    - Margaret J. Winkler Mintz & Bob and Katherine Fish (daughter of M.J. Winkler Mintz); December 2, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40.0226)
      Audiocassette, TDK D60
    - Phone interview with George Winkler; December 3, 1989 | Phone interview with Joe D'Angelo (King Features Press); December 21, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40.0227)
    - John Canemaker speaks with Terry Guy on "Felix, the Twisted Tale of the World's Most Famous Cat," KPFK 90.7 FM, Los Angeles, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 40.0228)
    - Phone interview with Jerry and Fanny Babitsky Rabin (Art Babbitt's sister); March 22, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 40.0229)
    - Elsie Babbitt; October 14, 1993 | Shamus Culhane; September 20, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40.023)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90
    - Ray Favata on Bill Tytla & NYC animation for TV in 1950's, 60's, 70's; November 29, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40.0231)
      Audiocassette, TDK SA-X 90
    - Disney animators, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40.0232)
    - John Canemaker, FRESH AIR, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40.0233)
      Audiocassette
    - Kathy Rose; December 28, 1993 | John Hench; January 6, 1994, 1993, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40.0234)
    - Joe Grant; January 7, 1994 | Marc Davis; January 10, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40.0235)
    - Marc Davis, Fletridge, CA; January 10, 1994 | Frank Thomas & Ollie Johnston, Fletridge, CA; January 11, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40.0236)
    - Kaleidoscope: Cardiff, Wales radio show hosted by Brian Sibley and featuring interviews with John Canemaker, Robin Allan, Joanna Quinn & Bob Godfrey; May 18, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40.0237)
    - Faith Hubley interview by John Canemaker, Parts I & II, Bridgehampton, NY; June 21, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 40.0238)
      Audiocassette, Sony 90
    - Faith Hubley interview, Parts III; July 20, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 40.0239)
    - Nick Park, NYU; October 21, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 40.024)
    - Chuck Jones phone interview with John Canemaker on Tex Avery, c. 1996 (Box 7, Folder 40.0241)
    - Brenda Chapman, Steve Hickner & Simon Wells interview by John Canemaker on PRINCE OF EGYPT; August 12, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 40.0242)
      Audiocassette, Fuji DR-I 60
    - Peter Lord, Nick Park & Jeffrey Katzenberg on CHICKEN RUN; March 16, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 40.0243)
    - Fred Schwartz on FINIAN'S RAINBOW; January 15, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40.0244)
      Audiocassette, Fuji DR-I 90
    - Raman Hui, William Steig (creator of Shrek), Vicky Jenson & Andrew Adamson on SHREK, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40.0245)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UR 120
    - Blue Sky interviews: Chuck Richardson, Mike Defeo (Lead Modeler) & John Donkin (Associate Producer) on ICE AGE; November 28, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40.0246)
    - Blue Sky interviews: Brian McEntee & Carlos Saldanha on ICE AGE; November 28, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40.0247)
    - Blue Sky interviews: Chris Wedge (Co-Director), Jerry David (Pre-Production), Dan Sheffelman (Story) & Moroni Taylor; November 28, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40.0248)
    - Karal Ann Marling; January 14, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 40.0249)
    - Pete Docter & Richard Williams from Pixar; March 15, 2002 | Maggie Rich (Mary Blair's niece) on Mary Blair; March 17, 2002 | Clark Spencer & Chris Sanders from Disney; March 19, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 40.025)
    - Rolly Crump; April 23, 2002 | Frank Thomas; April 24, 2002 | Kevin Blair; April 30, 2002 | Neil Graner; May 1, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 40.0251)
    - Alice Davis, Los Angeles; June 11, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 40.0252)
    - Tissa David; September 18, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 40.0253)
    - Joe Grant; April 11, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 40.0254)
    - Andreas Hykade & Jacob Schuh (Studio 501), Ludwigsburg, Germany; November 28, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 40.0255)
    - Pixar interviews: Ed Catmull (President of Pixar) interview by John Canemaker on THE INCREDIBLES; June 23, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40.0256)
    - Pixar interviews: Mark Andrews (Story Supervisor), Steve Hunter, Alan Barillaro & Tony Fucile (Supervising Animators) & Katherine Sarafin (Production Manager) on THE INCREDIBLES; June 23, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40.0257)
    - Pixar interviews: Brad Bird (Director) interview by John Canemaker on THE INCREDIBLES; June 24, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40.0258)
    - Pixar interviews: Rick Sayre (Supervising Technical Director) on THE INCREDIBLES; June 24, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40.0259)
    - George E. & Deborah Miller (brother/sister-in-law of John Parr Miller), Part I; November 15, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 40.026)
    - George E. Miller, Part II; November 15, 2005 | John Parr Miller; November 30, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 40.0261)
    - The Openended Group: Paul Kaiser, Shelley Eshkar & Marc Donnie; April 11, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 40.0262)
    - George Nicholson (literary agent) on Disney story artist J.P. Miller and Golden Books Publishing; May 31, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 40.0263)
    - Margot MacDonald Bachman on J.D. Miller, Hampshire House, 150 CPS, NYC; December 5, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 40.0264)
- Accretions 2008 - Series VI: Major Projects
  - Subseries A: "The Art and Flair of Mary Blair"
    - Book reviews, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Events: various related to book, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Publicity, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Blair, Mary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Blair, Donovan, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Blair, Kevin, 1994 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Blair, Lee ***see also*** Blair, Mary, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Blair, Preston ***see*** Blair, Lee, 1988
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to book (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Canemaker, John: Interviews: various related to research, 1994 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Canemaker, John: Notes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Canemaker, John: Powerpoint lecture on Mary Blair, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Canemaker, John: Research, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Chamberlain, Jeanne, 1994 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Crump, Roland, 1995 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Davis, Marc & Alice, 1994 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Disney, Walt: South American trip: General, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Disney, Walt: South American trip: AQUERELLA DO BRASIL, 1941 - 1942 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Disney, Walt: South American trip: SALUDOS AMIGOS, 1941 - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Grant, Joe, 1994 - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Grauer, Neil, 1994 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Johnston, Ollie ***see*** Thomas, Frank, 1995
    - Richardson, Margaret @ Maggie Rich, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Robinson, Varda, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Thomas, Frank, 1995 - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Subseries B: "The Animated Raggedy Ann & Andy"
    - Bell, Carl, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 141)